(Episode 2)
(This is a work of fiction.)
Who are you?
What is this place?
Don't do anything rash. I'm a barrister.
I can...
Yau Yam Yam,
I hereby declare that your life is over.
You were supposed to live until 70,
but you've committed too many sins.
Your life is cut short to 31.
You deserve this retribution.
Your crimes are...
How should I put it?
- Too many to list. - Far too many to list.
I can't be bothered to count them all.
Anyway, I sentence you to 721 counts of torture.
First, we'll sever your tongue.
You...
Wait.
What should I do first?
If I sever her tongue first,
and she can't scream, won't that be less satisfying?
Chop it off first.
Wait.
There's no need for theatrics in the netherworld.
Right. It's a force of habit.
King of Hell, I have a humble request.
You're interfering with my execution.
If your reason isn't good enough,
I'll sever your tongue too.
Well, I want to help Yau Yam Yam return to life.
Actually, her natural lifespan hasn't ended yet.
It has just been cut short by you, Your Majesty.
If you could be a little lenient,
I believe she can return to the mortal world.
Your Majesty, please take a look.
There's more.
Fusen red soil agarwood, Indian rosewood,
Hollong tree incense, and Bome musk.
The four most famous fragrances in the world.
I wonder if these will make you...
a little more lenient?
Why are you helping her?
I want her to help me...
with my family matters in the mortal world.
Five days.
That's all?
Fine. Five days it is.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Let's go. We're leaving.
This way.
Let's go. Be careful.
Is this really hell?
The real deal.
Not what you expected, right?
Why did you help me?
My time is up. I can't return to life.
I can't handle things myself.
So I need someone...
who can bridge the gap between the living and the dead...
and is well-versed in the law to help me.
I've seen your methods.
You're the perfect barrister for me.
Help me distribute my estate.
I heard the King of Hell rarely lets anyone return to life.
I was just taking a chance.
I didn't expect it to go so smoothly.
It seems you really are special.
You didn't kill me just because you wanted me to help you,
did you?
With money comes insider information.
It's the same in the netherworld...
as it is in the world of the living.
I knew you were about to die anyway.
Why would I need to kill you?
Then do you know who killed me?
That, I don't know.
The King of Hell is fickle.
He might go back on his word.
I don't want to go back and have my tongue cut off.
Let's hurry up and lose them. Run.
Over there!
I have this.
Don't let them get away! After them!
- Lie down on it. - What?
This is where the underworld connects to the world of the living.
If you want to go back up, lie down.
Look up.
Has my wife...
come by?
I... I want to see my son.
- Where's the doctor? - He's on his way.
We can't wait. Let's start.
Mr. Shek, I'm Mr. Wong, a lawyer.
According to your instructions,
I will now formally help you...
draft your will as you wished.
I'll read the contents to you,
and you will sign it yourself,
witnessed by two other lawyers.
Do you understand?
I understand.
"I, Shek Chung,"
"hereby make my will as follows."
"I revoke all previous wills..."
"and declare this..."
"to be my last will and testament."
"I appoint my son, Shek Kwong Sing,"
“as the executor of my estate.”
“After deducting funeral expenses..."
"and other necessary costs,"
"I bequeath all assets to Shek Kwong Sing."
"If my wife, Kwok Miu Wah, claims any inheritance,"
"she shall be given a nominal one dollar."
Mr. Shek, do you understand and agree...
to the contents of this will?
Dad.
Dad!
What are you doing here?
- Step aside. - Dad doesn't want to see you.
Go away!
Get out!
All of you, step aside!
Shek Chung, how dare you just die like this?
Dad said he doesn't want to see you! Get out!
- Shut up! Wake up! - Calm down.
- You can't die! - Don't touch Dad!
He has already passed away!
He's not dead yet!
- Wake up! - He's gone!
- Don't die! - Don't touch my dad!
Wake up!
He's my husband!
We shouldn't air dirty laundry in public.
Taking family matters to court is one thing,
but what I'm most worried about now...
is that wicked woman stealing all my money.
Counselor Yau,
I've hired you to ensure...
that wicked woman doesn't get a single extra dollar...
from my estate.
The biggest dispute in your case is that...
when you signed that will,
there was no doctor present...
to certify your mental state.
Based on precedents, it's a bit difficult to handle.
Don't worry, I have evidence.
When I found out that wicked woman...
was plotting to take my money,
I personally wrote a new will.
I left everything to my son.
But I softened my heart after writing it.
I left it in a wooden box at the office.
I never sent it to the law firm.
Counselor Yau, if you find this will,
you can prove that...
I had long intended to rewrite it.
I wasn't mentally unfit,
nor was I misled by my son.
If you really had such a will,
you should have told your son to bring it to court.
I was in a daze before I died.
How could I remember so much?
I only remembered after I died.
I even tried to tell my son in a dream to go look for it.
But that son of mine is so useless.
You brat, stop building those models.
I left a will at the office.
Go find it!
Why are you sleeping here?
I dreamt I was building a Freedom model.
The one you said was hard to build?
I want to finish it. Let me sleep more.
Can't you just appear...
before your son directly like this?
Do you think seeing a ghost is that easy?
Certain conditions must be met.
Either you've just died,
or you're like yourself,
with a very strong yin energy.
So you want me...
to help you find the draft of the will...
for your son?
Exactly. You've got it.
You can see ghosts, and you're a lawyer.
The unscrupulous kind, at that.
You'll surely find a way...
to stop that woman from getting my money.
Is there a problem?
Not with you.
But what about the King of Hell?
Doesn't he want to take me back?
Are you sure he'll let me stay here?
Don't worry, I've already appeased him.
How did you appease him?
Your Majesty, is something wrong?
I've been thinking.
Returning to the mortal world is a serious matter.
This deal doesn't seem quite right.
Yes, I understand.
I wonder if this would be more appropriate.
Let me remind you.
Keep a close eye on Yau Yam Yam.
If she does anything bad again,
I'll bring her back at any time.
Yes.
The economy in the netherworld is as bad as it is in the mortal world.
So he'll take any chance to be greedy.
Plus, the King of Hell is fickle.
So the sooner we resolve this, the better.
As long as you stay focused and help me,
it should be fine.
What about after I help you?
Do I have to go back immediately after I'm done?
Go to my office tomorrow and find that draft first.
We'll worry about the rest later.
Don't you dare pull any tricks.
I'll be watching you from down there.
For anything urgent, take the mirror to my grave to find me.
Don't worry.
I won't leave you behind.
I'll find a way to stay alive.
(Negotiate with Shek Chung for more time in the mortal world.)
(Find out who killed me.)
(Doing evil deeds shortens lifespan. Does doing good deeds lengthen it?)
I hope it works.
What are you doing?
It's not ready yet.
I want to see the dashcam footage.
Who is this person?
Say something.
What happened?
What did he do to you?
Send this video to me.
Hello?
I need all the CCTV footage near Lok Wing Road...
at 1am last night.
I'm looking for someone.
I'll send you the video in a bit.
My car enthusiast friends are great at finding people.
They can help.
Hurry up.
I just want to help you.
Amber.
I know you don't want me to know what's going on,
but I'm very worried about you.
This is a ballpoint pen on one end...
and a spike on the other.
It can pierce through anything.
Take it for self-defense.
I'm only lending it to you.
You have to return it.
Ben.
Are you free?
I'm a bit busy today.
I'm feeling a bit down today.
Keep me company for a while.
Wait for me in the car.
I'll be right back.
She's Dee's wife.
So what? She's unhappy.
It's fine.
Excuse me.
I'd like to make a donation.
What?
I'd like to make an offering.
Just put it in that box.
Give me a certificate of appreciation...
to prove I'm charitable and earning merit.
I'll slowly add it in.
Red Cross Headquarters.
What's the matter?
Didn't I tell you to go to my office?
Why are you dawdling here?
I forgot to call my boss.
Hello?
He said I've done too many bad things,
shortening my life.
So I'll do more good deeds now...
to make sure I don't die right after helping you.
If I'm going to die right after completing your case,
then I'll definitely delay it.
You can't delay it!
The trial is ongoing. We need a quick resolution.
Go to my office now.
Fine, but let's go to the Red Cross first.
Because if I don't go today...
If you don't focus on this case,
I'll have the King of Hell take you back...
to have your tongue cut out!
Fine, I'll go. You don't have to be so fierce.
Counselor Yau is my apprentice.
She's trustworthy.
How did you know my dad's will is in the office?
I'm not at liberty to say.
How we find it doesn't matter.
What matters is the result.
In terms of investigation, if Counselor Yau is second,
even I wouldn't dare claim to be first.
She's absolutely trustworthy.
This way.
This unfilial son hasn't been back to the office for so long.
He doesn't even know where my room is.
Could it be over there?
That looks like the boss's office.
Where is it?
It's...
Over there.
Move those CDs, and you'll see a wooden box.
I put it inside.
Why do you...
Results are everything.
I forgot where I put the key.
Let me think about it.
Is it okay as long as I can open it?
Yes.
Thank you.
Impossible.
- Hey. - You...
Stomachache.
Where's the restroom?
Over there.
Her stomach hurts.
Are you kidding me?
I'm sure I put it in there.
It's one thing to drag me down,
but now you're dragging my master down too.
How is he supposed to explain this to the client?
A real man takes responsibility for his own actions.
I'll apologize to your master.
Can he even see you?
Think carefully.
Did you tell anyone else?
Could someone else have taken it?
I remember now.
That day, after I finished writing it at home...
Chung!
Take your medicine first.
Take it slow.
Where is the master?
He's in the study.
Why weren't you following him?
Always daydreaming.
Put it away first. Keep it in the wooden box at the office.
Here's the key.
That's how it was, right? You're not misremembering?
That's right. I remember correctly.
I really don't understand.
Why didn't you just have a lawyer handle it?
It would've been safe at a law firm.
We were married for so many years.
I wanted to leave some room for reconciliation.
Who knew that evil woman...
wouldn't even visit me once...
while I was in the hospital for so long?
We shared a bed for decades.
I didn't see her true colors until the moment I died.
I can't stay.
I've been in the world of the living too long.
I have to go back.
Go to Kwan Nga and get the will.
She was my former nurse. Hurry.
Where is Mr. Shek?
He's gone.
I'll definitely find that draft...
so you can fulfill your promise to Mr. Shek.
You're doing me a favor by helping.
Don't make it sound like it's your responsibility.
Get in the car.
Are you free tonight?
Dinner to celebrate your birthday?
Has your wife recovered?
Almost.
(Wife)
Hello?
Okay, I'll be right back. Bye.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Please help me one more time.
I'm begging you.
It's hard to get stock lately. Take them sparingly.
Can I have one more? Thank you.
When did you start taking these again?
The odds for this case...
have always been low.
But I represent the side of justice.
My wife, my father-in-law,
and the whole world thinks I'll win.
I'll definitely find that draft.
How do you know it exists?
I know his nurse.
I'm really losing my touch.
I even missed a key point like this.
That's enough.
I don't want to do...
shady things anymore.
Let's change our ways together, okay?
I'll take you home first.
The medicine made me thirsty.
Can you buy me a bottle of water?
Master.
Master!
Send an ambulance immediately.
I'm on First Street. Someone fainted.
What should I do now?
CPR?
I don't know how to do CPR.
I'll go find someone.
Do you know how to perform CPR?
Sir, do you know how to perform CPR?
CPR.
Master.
The ambulance is here. Hang in there.
Please be okay.
You have to be okay.
I didn't say anything.
I've arranged to transfer you to Yan Wo.
Dr. Chan will follow up.
No need. I'm fine. Help me process my discharge.
Did my wife look for me?
I've asked Bella to tell her...
that you need to review a case tonight.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Think about what you really want.
Is this how you want to keep going?
I'm leaving. Get some rest.
Where are the pills?
They're still in your car.
Don't worry.
Tomorrow, I'll be...
the same Yeung Kam Tsuen that you all know.
Don't worry.
Please focus.
What clues have we missed?
Didn't I say there was a draft?
Go find Kwan Nga.
What are you still digging for here?
I've already sent someone to find her.
One can never have too much evidence, old man.
You're calling me an old man?
I'm strong enough to kill tigers! Old man?
Wait.
That ungrateful son...
installed CCTV at the front door.
What were they saying that day?
Does it record audio?
The one at my house does.
That ungrateful son must have used the same technician.
While Mr. Shek Chung was being treated for lung cancer,
you transferred about 30 million in cash from his accounts...
into your personal account, right?
- Yes. - Why did you do that?
Those were birthday gifts from him.
He was in poor health and authorized me to handle it.
Why would he suddenly transfer 30 million in cash...
to you as a birthday gift?
Maybe he knew his time was short.
He wanted to provide me with security.
That's strange.
You are Shek Chung's legal wife.
Even if he didn't have a will,
half of his estate would go to you after his death.
Was it because your relationship changed?
He didn't like you, and you were afraid he would divorce you,
so you transferred the money?
Your Honor, I object.
No. I'm Mrs. Shek, and I always will be.
Don't talk nonsense here.
Witness, please watch your language.
Please turn to page 33 of the bundle.
Who is she?
She was my husband's nurse.
She was Mr. Shek Chung's nurse, Ms. Leung Kwan Nga.
You complained about her to the agency many times.
Yes.
Because she did a poor job and was irresponsible.
If she was so bad, why didn't you fire her?
Because Chung always said to give young people a chance.
Now, playing the footage referenced on page 40,
a clip on the USB drive.
It is CCTV footage showing the defendant, Shek Kwong Sing,
outside his own home.
Can you explain what was happening then?
The nurse took Chung away without my permission.
I was arguing with her.
Why do you keep asking about that woman?
She has nothing to do with our family matters.
Your Honor,
Ms. Leung is highly relevant to this case.
Please allow me to play the video again.
Please turn the volume to the maximum.
It actually has audio.
The recording is just very faint.
It's so quiet that no one noticed,
but we have prepared an amplifier.